<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RabbitHole | A Nerd-Controlled Blog</title>
    <description>The life and unlife of a nerd called Hugo</description>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 17:52:40 +0200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 17:52:40 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.5.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>What we leave behind</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-we-leave-behind&quot;&gt;What we leave behind&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;I woke up yesterday morning like any other day since I’ve been in Groningen. Woke up normally, got dressed lazily, went downstairs and had breakfast and continued forth with my day. But I did not go to bed like any other day. As fate, or karma or coincidence or whatever post-modernists call today to the unavoidable unknowing reality that is what happens to us, would have it, it decided to after months of consistent normality, give me a happy moment. You may say that it is good that it happened. You may say that it...</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 17:06:16 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>/what-we-leave-behind/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/what-we-leave-behind/</guid>
        
        <category>Special</category>
        
        <category>Feelings</category>
        
        
        <category>Random</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to my blog</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;greetings-and-salutations&quot;&gt;Greetings and salutations!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My name is Hugo and welcome to my blog/personal website - RabbitHole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll find here information about me here and some posts about what I think and do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe you’ll find some of my friend’s thoughts too!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll try (and most likely fail) to post weekly about a random topic that I find relevant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Until then,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;cite&gt; Hugo&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2018 23:31:17 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>/welcome-to-my-blog/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/welcome-to-my-blog/</guid>
        
        <category>Welcome</category>
        
        <category>Greeting</category>
        
        <category>And</category>
        
        <category>Salutations</category>
        
        
        <category>Random</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Train Social Engineering</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Since my first year of college I’ve had to commute by train twice a week. It’s a 2 hour journey and after finishing all of my “To Read” List and listening to all of the podcasts my phone can hold, I’ve needed something else to occupy my mind. I resorted to people watch, but instead of watching the passengers I felt drawn to the conductor. Specifically, why he asked certain people for tickets and others he just ignored. See, in Portugal the conductor doesn’t ask for your ticket when you’re boarding the train. He asks for it after the train...</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>/train-social-engineering/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/train-social-engineering/</guid>
        
        <category>Social Engineering</category>
        
        <category>Portugal</category>
        
        <category>SE</category>
        
        
        <category>Social Engineering</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
